One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan aru nda
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
Off the Coast
of Laboratory 8
"Cruel Fate -
Kuma's Decision as a Father"
"Justice"
I'm here on business.
It's really cold here...
It's totally different from Punk Hazard.
I'll recreate the very future of humankind here.
I'm having trouble dealing with
the constant flow of new ideas!
And yet...
...you didn't know
this laboratory inside out.
What brought you here?
Every conversation here was overheard.
It's not good to
secretly negotiate with a pirate.
Shut up!
It's that side of you, Borsalino!
I don't like that side of you!
Look, I'm sorry...
But this is what I do...
Is this Borsalino?
Yes, I arrived.
You are there, aren't you, Vegapunk?
Yeah...
This may not concern you, Vegapunk...
...but even if Bartholomew Kuma would make
an excellent base for the clone soldiers,
he is a notorious pirate
with a bounty of 296 million berries.
The Marines would lose face...
...by possessing clone soldiers
based on such a man.
Saving face isn't important to science!
If the cloning project succeeds,
many lives will be saved!
Certainly, if your plan succeeds,
we will gain immense power.
So here are additional conditions.
The first is, Bartholomew Kuma,
you will join the Seven
Warlords of the Sea as a pirate.
The other day, a rookie named Ace
took down one of the Warlords,
and we have been
looking for a replacement.
The world of pirates
is becoming turbulent.
You would be perfect for a Warlord.
The second is,
Kuma, you will become
the Marines' human weapon yourself.
What?!
You mean, I must get my body modified?
That is correct.
As a Warlord, that unique power will pose
a significant threat to pirates.
That would help the Marines a lot.
Shut up, Kizaru!
Certainly.
But Kuma also has a prior record
of Revolutionary activity.
We do not want him to use that power
against the World Government.
So the third condition...
...is that you must ultimately abandon
your mind and free will.
Wait!
That's a death sentence, St. Saturn!
Is this because the other Warlords
won't do what you want?!
A cyborg without free will
is a soulless robot!
Are you telling me to become a murderer?!
You are in no position to argue with me.
You are the Marines' scientist.
Those are the three conditions
for saving the life of a criminal's daughter.
If you cannot accept them,
we have no obligation...
...to spend a fortune on surgeries
to save some nameless girl.
It's dangerous for you to run in here!
This is...
...murder...
It's inhumane to perform
such a modification surgery...
Vegapunk.
I want you to do it.
Kuma...
I thought he'd make impossible demands
and I wouldn't be able to save Bonney!
I was on pins and needles!
Thank you.
If Bonney gets well,
I will gladly accept any fate!
Kuma!
Sentomaru-san,
about the matter we discussed...
- Yeah.
- Heave-ho!
Hey!
Get back here!
Vegapunk...
How long will it take for Kuma's modification
and his daughter's full treatment?
Sapphire Scales surgeries
will take six months,
and she'll have to wait
another year before she goes outside.
So a year and a half in total.
It'll take at least two years
for Kuma's modification.
I'm so glad...
Bonney will get well
before her tenth birthday!
Your daughter is essentially a hostage.
Once she recovers,
you will no longer need to obey us.
I won't run!
Just to be safe,
the World Government
will take custody of her after her surgeries.
Once you lose your free will,
she will be granted freedom.
Then, Kuma won't get to see her
again after she gets well!
I guess not.
Moving forward,
Kuma will undergo modification surgeries...
...while ruling the seas
as a pirate from the Seven Warlords.
Once her surgeries are complete,
he will be forbidden to contact her or escape.
If you violate that rule,
your daughter will be enslaved.
I will never see her!
But I just have one request!
I don't want her to know
the truth about her disease
or the fact that she is a hostage!
So after her surgeries, instead of making
her stay at some drab government facility,
I want you to let her rest at the church
in the Sorbet Kingdom where she grew up!
If you do that,
I promise I'll never go there to see her
and I'll do exactly as you command!
Very well.
As long as she is under watch,
it doesn't matter where.
These next two years
are going to be interesting.
Clank.
Dad!
Bonney!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
- Were you a good girl?
- Yeah!
Uncle!
Bonney, we're going to stay here
for the next six months.
What?! You're going to be here, too?!
Yeah, I've also found out I have an illness,
so I'm getting tested.
You too?! Yay!
This guy's Sentomaru!
"This guy"?
She is a handful,
but please look after her.
Fine...
Thank you.
Dad!
There are so many rooms
without windows here!
Yeah... No, but there are
dangerous things too, so...
Oh, it's fine! You're too much of a chicken!
Oh hey, Bonney!
Darn... Darn... Darn!
I'll create the weapons of my dreams!
Ideas keep flowing!
Somebody, help write out what's in my brain!
Eat for me! Go to the bathroom for me!
I'm too busy! I want to rage!
Oh, I got another idea!
I'd welcome even a cat's help!
If only there were five more of me!
Hey!
Sentomaru!
You holding up?
Are you free?! I bet you are!
I can play with you!
I'm not free!
Aw, really?
Look, I don't have time to hang out with you
every day...
J-Just for a little while, okay?
Yay!
Oh, hey...
Oh, Dad!
Bonney!
Your daughter...
...lacks any sense of modesty.
Isn't it nice? He's my horsey!
Yeah, it is nice, Bonney!
B-Bonney...
Don't ask too much of him...
Okay!
I don't think she gets it...
Dad!
What is it, Bonney?
H-How did you get so stained?!
Ta-dah!
"Dad"
This is for you!
Thank you! I'll treasure it!
"Dad"
Oh, that's a VIP seat, Bonney!
All right, Bonney-chan. See you tomorrow.
Okay...
I'm hungry...
This smell must be...
Oh, Bonney!
I was just about to come get you.
Let's eat it together!
Pizza!
So good!
Cheers!
Hey, Dad! Let's do that thing!
Oh!
This is the Nika Dance!
Let's dance together!
Let me try...
Like this?
That's it!
This is quite hard.
You're no fun...
Uncle!
A-All right...
Six Months Later
Great! You're doing well!
In another year,
you'll be completely cured.
Thank you, Vegapunk!
Thank you!
Um...
Once I get well,
can I come visit?!
Of course!
Dad!
Is the sea beautiful?
Yes, it's beautiful.
I wanna see it...
You'll be able to see it soon.
Yeah!
With you!
Yeah... Can't wait.
Sorbet Kingdom
Bonney! Kumachi! Welcome home!
It's been a long time!
You can live here again?
Yes!
I'll be cured in a year
and get to go outside!
Oh yeah?! I'm happy for you.
You said you'd get well before age ten
and you were right!
Does somebody need to be
looked after again?
Queen Dowager Conney,
Sorbet Kingdom
Old Bag Conney!
We'll all be happy
to take care of her, Kuma.
Leave her to us!
Thank you. I'll be relying on you again.
I'm a pirate now,
so I may cause this country trouble...
I probably won't be able to
come back for over a year.
What?! For that long?!
I'll write you a lot!
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Next time we meet, let's be out on the sea,
watching the horizon together.
Yeah! Can't wait!
And I wanna go on many trips!
Yeah! I would love to
take you anywhere you like!
I would've loved to do it...
Leave it all to me, Kuma-san.
Alpha, an Intelligence Agent
Cipher Pol No.8
Who is this woman?!
By the doctor's orders,
I'll stay with Bonney-chan
until she's fully cured.
Every day, I'll check her temperature,
administer medicine,
and monitor for even the slightest changes!
I'm Alpha, a nurse!
Nice to meet you, Bonney-chan.
Hey! What did you build out in front?!
That's our temporary housing!
Until she's fully cured,
we can't let anyone suspicious see her,
so always carry your ID, everyone.
So inconvenient!
A child's neck...
Can be crushed just like that.
I know.
I'll never come back.
Thank you, Bonney.
For being born.
What?!
Okay, I'm heading out.
Take care!
Don't worry about Bonney!
Despite being called the Tyrant,
Bartholomew Kuma was very obedient to orders, and his joining the Seven Warlords...
"Seven Warlords of the Sea"
...shook up pirates across the world.
Young Master. It says
there's a new member of the Seven Warlords.
Kuma the Tyrant?
We've got another miscreant on our hands.
Are you interested in the new Warlord?
I don't care who it is.
Anyway,
have you eliminated the witness
to our Rainmaking Ship?
Yes, flawlessly.
He's supposedly as huge as Whitebeard.
Who's stronger? Me or him?
Koby.
O-Of course, it's you, Alvida-sama!
Jinbe! They found a replacement!
I'm happy for you.
Who are you to say that, Ace?
There would be no fuss
if you didn't defeat Hanafuda in the first place.
Do you think this new face
will meet your approval?
I'm trying to see that now.
A former king?!
Well, there is an active king
in the group as well.
The world of pirates has changed...
It does not matter to me.
Because I will never go to the central!
Even so, you still need to know these things,
Snake Princess!
Hey!
It says he's a Paw Pad Human!
What kind of power is that?!
But Moria-sama, he's a Warlord!
The Seven Warlords work
directly under the Government, right?!
Kuma-san wouldn't join such a group!
"Dear Bonney, I'm writing to you at sea.
"Dad"
I became a little famous,
so it is difficult to travel now,
but I'm doing okay."
Sorry, it's far. Thanks.
"How's everyone?
I'll try to find many places...
...that I would like to visit with you
when you turn ten."
Bartholomew Kuma,
you have a new order from the Government.
Where are you?
It's mad!
I'm in the East Blue.
What is the order?
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
EVERYDAY makerenai
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kiduita no